barstoolsports.net 2017-06-24

# Barstool Sports

**Privacy Policy**

Welcome to _Barstool Sports_ , which you may be accessing through our website or its related sites (collectively, “Website”) or our mobile app (“App”) (the Website and App will sometimes be collectively referred to as the “Platform”).  The Platform is operated by Barstool Sports, Inc. (“we,” “us,” or “our”).  We believe that the privacy and security of your information and data (“Information”) is very important.  This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains the type of Information we collect from users of the Platform, how that Information is used, how the Information may be shared with other parties, and what controls our users have regarding their Information. We encourage you to read this Policy carefully.  Any updates or modifications to this Policy will be posted to our website on this page. By using or accessing the Platform, you signify that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy.  This Policy is effective as of May 24, 2017 and has not been modified since that date.

Information We Collect

There are two types of Information that may be collected through our Platform: (1) “Personal Information” such as your name, e-mail address, physical address, phone number, credit card number and other information that can be used to directly identify you, and (2) “Usage Data” which is data related to your use of the Platform (e.g., the pages you visit, the sites you use before or after visiting ours) or anonymous information about the computer or device used to access the Platform (e.g., your IP address or device ID).

You may enter the Platform and browse its content without submitting any Personal Information.  However, if you wish to establish an account, make a purchase through our store, contact us, subscribe or opt in to our newsletter, alerts, or other communications, communicate with another user, post any comments, submit user content, participate in a contest, or otherwise communicate with us in any way, we may at that time require that you provide certain Personal Information such as your name or username, e-mail address and physical address. When you submit Personal Information through the Platform, whether by directly providing it to us upon request or voluntarily disclosing it through comments, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

If you choose to connect to our Platform through a third-party social network such as Facebook, Twitter or Instagram (each, a “Social Network”), we may collect Personal Information from your profile on such Social Network, such as your name, username, and e-mail address, and we may publish your activity on our Platform through such Social Network. In addition, our Platform may offer social sharing features which will allow you to “Share” or “Like” on a Social Network. If you decide to use such features, it may allow the sharing and collection of Information both to and from such Social Network so you should check the privacy policy of each Social Network before using such features.

A note about your profile and comments: if you choose to include Personal Information in your profile (such as your name), that Information will be publicly-facing and, therefore, be visible to other users.  In addition, any content you post will obviously be available to the public so if you do not want Personal Information made public, do not include any in your profile or any comments you may post.

Whether or not you submit Personal Information, any time you visit our Platform, we may collect, store or accumulate certain Usage Data based on your use of our Platform, such as information regarding which of our pages you viewed, which products you purchased, the method by which you were directed to our Platform, the URLs you visited before and after using our Website, the browser you use, your computer’s IP address, or your device ID or other persistent identifier.

Please note that we will only collect your credit card information if you choose to purchase our products online via our Platform.  If you do make such an online purchase, our payment processing partner will collect your payment information and process your payment.  We do not store any credit card information or share it with anyone other than our payment processor.

Uses and Sharing of Information

We use your Personal Information that we collect to send you newsletters, push notifications or other communications you have opted into, fulfill your orders, authenticate website visits/usage, process your requests, inform you of relevant products and content through promotional e-mails, register you for a contest and process any prize you may win, and otherwise communicate with you.  You always will be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from further emails in any promotional messages we send you.

We contract with companies or individuals to provide certain services including email and hosting services, e-commerce services, software development, credit card processing, shipping and fulfillment, data management, surveys and marketing, promotional services, contests, etc.  We call them our “Service Providers.” We may share both your Personal Information and Usage Data with Service Providers solely as appropriate for them to perform their services for us.  We do not share your credit card or other account information with third parties unless you authorize us to do so, or if it is necessary to fulfill our responsibilities including, but not limited to, delivering a product or service that you order.

Except as described above, we will not disclose, rent, sell or share any Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes.

Usage Data may be used in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as optimizing the platform, generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may also use, share or transfer such aggregated, anonymized Usage Data with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners for administrative, analytical, research, optimization, security and other purposes, but no such information will be linked with your Personal Information or be used to identify or contact you.

Finally, we may share your Information: (i) In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us; (ii) When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others; and in connection with the enforcement of our Terms of Use and other agreements; or (iii) In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Privacy and Security 

It is entirely your choice whether or not you provide Personal Information to us. We take reasonable precautions to protect our customers’ Personal Information against loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, please remember that no transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any Information that you transmit to us or from us, and you do so at your own risk. You hereby acknowledge that we are not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

In addition, while we take reasonable steps to govern our Service Providers’ use and protection of your Personal Information, we ultimately have no control over and are not responsible for the privacy practices of such parties. As a condition to your use of the Platform, you expressly agree we bear no responsibility, and are not liable in any way, for the acts, omissions or policies of our Service Providers or any other external sources with respect to your Information

If you believe your Personal Information is being improperly used by us or any third party, please immediately notify us via email at privacy@barstoolsports.com.

**_Cookies_**

**_We, or third party advertisers or content providers on our Platform, may use cookies or similar tracking technologies like web beacons, JavaScript, clear gifs, and log files. These “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are generally stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive or on third party servers. Generally, Cookies work by assigning to your computer or device a unique ID that has no meaning outside of the Platform.   Cookies are used for a variety of reasons, including for the storage of your Information so you don’t have to re-enter it, the collection of Usage Data, and the tracking of your entries and submissions. Our Cookies do not generally contain any personally identifying information. Most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, but you can usually configure your browser to prevent this. However, not accepting Cookies may make certain features of the Platform unavailable to you. _**

Children Under 13

This website is intended for and targeted to adults.  We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information directly from anyone under the age of 13.  If you are under 13, please do not send any Personal Information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.  If you are a parent or guardian of a child under 13 years of age and you believe your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at privacy@barstoolsports.com.    

If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of the Platform, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you have publicly posted. To make such a request, please send an email with a detailed description of the specific content or information to privacy@barstoolsports.com and include “CA Removal Request” in the subject line. Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested.

**Opting Out**

At various times during your use of the Platform, you may be presented with the ability to “opt in” to receiving newsletters, push notifications or other communications from us, including those promotional in nature.  If you do not want to receive such communications, do not opt in.  Alternatively, if you initially decide to receive communications from us but at a later date wish to remove your information from our database, you can do so by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our communications.  You may also at any time opt out of receiving communications from us by sending an e-mail to privacy@barstoolsports.com with the subject line “Opt Out.”

Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our communications, we may still need to contact you with important information related to your account and your purchases.  For example, even if you have unsubscribed from our promotional emails, we will still send you confirmation of a purchase you have made on our Platform.

Links to Third Party Platforms

Our Platform or communications may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation, including the form of advertising, embedded content, sponsored content or co-branded content.  Except as set forth in this Policy, we do not share your Personal Information with those third parties and are not responsible for the privacy policies of any third party or their management of your Personal Information. Because they may treat your Information differently than we do, we suggest you read the privacy policies on those third party websites prior to submitting any Personal Information to such sites.

Advertisers

Our Platform may contain advertisements for third parties that are served through third party ad servers or ad networks.  These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Platform. Through the use of technologies such as Cookies, they automatically receive certain Usage Data (such as your IP address or device identifier) which they use to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

In some cases, certain advertisers may use Usage Data collected through our Platform to engage in online behavioral advertising. To opt-out of the use of Cookies by over 50 major third party behavioral advertising providers, please visit: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.

We may participate in affiliate advertising and allow affiliate links to be encoded on some of our pages. This means that we may earn a commission when you click on or make purchases via affiliate links and affiliate partners may use Cookies to understand your use of the Platform.

Your Rights and Obligations 

You represent and warrant that any Personal Information you provide us is true and correct and relates to you and not to any other person.

If you wish to review, delete and/or revise the Personal Information we have stored about you, please contact us with your specific request at privacy@barstoolsports.com; provided, however, that we reserve the right to retain an archive of such Personal Information for a commercially reasonable time to ensure that its deletion does not affect the integrity of our data; and we further reserve the right to retain an anonymous version of such Information.

If you use the Platform, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and for restricting access to your computer or device, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account.

Your California Privacy Rights

Under certain circumstances, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 states that, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, a business may be required to provide detailed information regarding how that business has shared that customer’s Personal Information with third parties for direct marking purposes. However, the foregoing does not apply to businesses like ours that do not disclose Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes without prior approval or give customers a free mechanism to opt out of having their personal information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. California users may request further information about their rights under this law and our policy by writing to us at privacy@barstoolsports.com, using the subject line “CA Request for Information,” and requesting further information.

California Do Not Track Disclosures:  For various technical reasons, our Platform may not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. In the event we make changes to this Policy, such policy will be re-posted in the “Privacy” section of our Platform with the date such modifications were made indicated on the top of the page. Therefore, please review this Policy from time to time so that you are aware when any changes are made to this Policy.  If you have any questions about the changes that were implemented, please contact us at privacy@barstoolsports.com and include “Information Regarding Updated Policy” in the subject line.  In any event, your continued use of the Platform after such change constitutes your acceptance of any such change(s), and if you do not accept any changes, you may choose not to use the Platform or opt out by sending us an appropriate notice.

If you have questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us at privacy@barstoolsports.com with “Platform Privacy” in the subject line of your email.
